<forums>

<forum>
        <name>Hrvatska</name>
        <description>You're free to ask questions or discuss anything in English. Note that the answer to some of your questions might already be in the links below. To those replying to questions – be polite.</description>
        <categories>
            <category>HUMOR</category>
            <category>ORIGINAL CONTENT</category>
            <category>INTERESTING</category>
            <category>NEWS</category>
            <category>META</category>
            <category>ASK</category>
            <category>SERIOUS</category>
        </categories>
        <owner>T_0ni</owner>
        <moderators>
        	<moderator>powrtothemoon</moderator>
        </moderators>
        <rules>Please respect all Reddit rules as well as the reddiquette.
Posting of personal information is strongly forbidden, for example names, surnames, address, Facebook profiles, etc. This also means not posting your own personal information as there is no way to verify whether it's your own personal information.
If you want to get in touch with a redditor, use private messages.
This subreddit is not for seeking friends, family or soul mates. Do not stalk or obsess over other users.
In the event of a potential meetup, redditors might create a Facebook event or use similar methods of communication. Signing up to such events will be done at your own risk.
You are not allowed to advertise legal entities in your posts. Links to some blog post or article of yours are fine, as long as they are not your only posts on this subreddit.
If you'd like to advertise on Reddit, use Reddit's own ad platform. There you can also choose to display advertisements only to readers of this subreddit.
If you're not sure whether your post constitutes spam or not, contact the moderators.
You're not allowed to promote illegal or harmful content and/or violence. Discussions about these subjects are banned.
For example, posts talking about use of drugs is welcome, but posts talking about acquiring drugs are not welcome.
Posts that attack or discriminate a minority based on generalizations or stereotypes are not allowed.
Behave in a civilized manner. Vulgar language is not forbidden, but excessive and unnecessary use thereof might result in your post being deleted.
NSFW content must be properly marked. NSFW (Not Safe For Work) content includes erotic, violent or vulgar content.
As a rule of thumb, something that would be for a 15+ audience on TV is NSFW.
This is not an NSFW subreddit - submitting NSFW content unrelated to the subreddit's subject or a specific post is strictly forbidden.
Moderators are not to abuse their powers and not to use their position to force their opinion on others.
You can reach us at any time via the modmail contact form.
Titles must concisely describe its content or intention. Posts with generic titles which are too generic, false or heavily editorialized will be removed.
Excessive posting or excessive linking to a single source might be cause for a ban. The moderators will issue a warning beforehand.
Low effort memes are not allowed.
"Low effort" is considered to be a meme made with meme generators (e.g. Imgflip), or all that would otherwise be found on meme subreddits, Facebook pages or Instagram accounts dedicated to memes. Also, a hastily composed image with two, three lines of text is considered a "low effort".
It is permitted to post meme as a comment on a thread that has been inspired or linked to meme.</rules>
        <created>1589026805</created>
        <subscribers>3</subscribers>
    </forum>
    <forum>
        <name>Jokes</name>
        <description>Welcome to Jokes</description>
        <categories>
            <category>All Jokes</category>
        </categories>
        <owner>powrtothemoon</owner>
        <moderators/>
        <rules>Offensive jokes are fine as long as they are still jokes. We do make exceptions for extremely offensive jokes.

Reddit prohibits any sexual or suggestive content involving minors.

Keep the comment section civil and light hearted.

Personal attacks will not be tolerated. If you want to be a dick, go to /r/insults

Jokes must be in text format, no emojis or linking allowed. (YouTube, Imgur, etc)

As a measure to prevent spam and reposts we are limiting the number of jokes a user can submit to 3 every 24 hours.

This subreddit is not a platform for blatant self-promotion

If you post a NSFW image/link in the comments, it must be tagged as NSFW (Nudity/gross images) or NSFL (Gore/extremely disturbing images, and only if relevant to the conversation)

Jokes must be in English</rules>
        <created>1589031819</created>
        <subscribers>0</subscribers>
    </forum>
<forum>
        <name>Europe</name>
        <description>European diskuto
edited</description>
        <categories>
            <category>EU</category>
        </categories>
        <owner>admin</owner>
        <moderators>
            <moderator>powrtothemoon</moderator>
        </moderators>
        <rules>TBD</rules>
        <created>1593805571</created>
        <subscribers>2</subscribers>
    </forum>
<forum><name>Funny</name><description>Funny Diskuto... Opis uskoro</description><categories><category>MEMES</category><category>JOKES</category><category>LOL</category></categories><owner>DaftFunk11</owner><moderators/><rules>Please note:

    - Hate speech and bigotry will be removed at the moderators' discretion.

    - Bots and bot-like accounts are not allowed.

    - No link shorteners (or HugeURL) in either post links or comments. They will be deleted regardless of intent. This is an anti-spam measure.</rules><created>1594245207</created><subscribers>1</subscribers></forum><forum><name>Sport</name><description>Sport Diskuto</description><categories><category>Football</category><category>Basketball</category><category>Tennis</category><category>Formula 1</category></categories><owner>dbogovic</owner><moderators/><rules>Some rules...</rules><created>1594480368</created><subscribers>0</subscribers></forum></forums>